Guide to the Sports Information Office: Photographic Negatives collection, circa 1924-1992, 1995, undated UA.13.02.0018
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- General Athletics Negatives, 1928-1979; undated; 9
  - Individual Athletes/Coaches/Staff, 33
    - Woodyard, Lorraine (Assistant Athletic Director), 1977 (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03854)
  - Groups, 34
    - Coaches, unidentified, 1928, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05853)
    - Coaches, unidentified, 1929, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05854)
    - Coaches (Emerson "Curly" Sanders (football, wrestling, boxing), Eddie Cameron (football, basketball), James DeHart (Athletic Director, football), Tex Tilson (football, wrestling, boxing), Lenox Baker (trainer)), 1930, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05855)
    - Coaches (Eddie Cameron, Tex Tilson, James DeHart), 1930, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05856)
    - Athletics Staff, unidentified, 1931, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05857)
    - Coaches, unidentified, 1931, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05858)
    - Coaches (K. C. "Gerry" Gerard, E. V. Mitchell (sports editor, Durham Herald Sun), John Heller), circa 1938, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05859)
    - Athletics Staff, unidentified, 1943 (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03855)
    - Instructors, unidentified, 1944, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05860)
    - Athletics Staff, unidentified, 1945, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05861)
    - Athletics Staff, unidentified, 1945 (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03856)
    - Training Staff, unidentified, 1950 (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03857)
    - Student Managers, unidentified, 1951 (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03858)
    - Student Managers, unidentified, 1952 (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03859)
    - Student Managers, unidentified, 1953 (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03860)
    - Athletics Staff, unidentified, 1954 (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03861)
    - Athletics Staff, unidentified, 1957 Sept. (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03862)
    - Athletics Staff, unidentified, 1958 Sept. (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03863)
    - Athletics Staff, unidentified, 1959 Sept. (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03864)
    - Athletics Staff, unidentified, 1960 (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03865)
    - Athletics Staff, unidentified, 1961 Sept. (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03866)
    - Duke Univ. Athletic Association (DUAA) Officials: unidentified, 1962 May (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03867)
    - Coaches, Eddie Cameron, Mike McGee, Terry Sanford (copy negative), 1972 (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03868)
    - Coaches, Eddie Cameron, Terry Sanford, and Carl James (standing by Cameron Indoor Stadium plaque), 1974 Feb. (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03869)
  - Miscellaneous, 35
    - Coaches' School, 1932, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05862)
    - Coaches' School, 1933, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05863)
    - Coaches' School, 1934, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05864)
    - Coaches' School, 1935, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05865)
    - Coaches' School, 1935, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05866)
    - Coaches' School, 1939 (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03870)
    - Coaches' School, 1940, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05867)
    - P. E. Class, circa 1940s, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05868)
    - Coaches' School, 1941 (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03871)
    - Coaches' School, 1955 Mar. (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03872)
    - Coaches' School, 1956 Mar. (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03873)
    - Player Awards (DeLoetch, Holler), 1956 Nov. (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03874)
    - Staff Awards, 1957 June (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03875)
    - Intramural Committee in Cameron's Office, 1964 May (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03876)
    - Big Four Sports Day Trophy, Intramural, 1967 Aug. (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03877)
    - Intramural Awards, 1968 May (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03878)
    - Intramural Awards, 1969 May (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03879)
    - Intramural Awards, 1970 (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03880)
    - Shoe for Otho Davis, 1970 Jan. (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03881)
    - Intramural Awards, 1974 May (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03882)
    - Intramural Awards, 1975 May (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03883)
    - Sports Hall of Fame Portraits (Sime, Murray, Souchak, Crawford) (color), 1976 (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03884)
    - Sports Hall of Fame Portraits (Marin, Cox, Baker, Mullins, Heyman) (color), 1978 (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03885)
    - Sports Hall of Fame Portraits (color), 1979 (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03886)
    - Sports Hall of Fame Portraits (color), 1980 (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03887)
    - Intramural Trophy, undated, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05869)
    - Gym Interior (copy negative), undated (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03888)
    - Youth Day (color), undated (Box 31, Item UA13020018-N-03889)
- Golf Negatives, 1928-1989; undated; 10
  - Individual Athletes/Coaches/Staff, 36
    - Aiken, Frank, 1946 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03890)
    - Alexander, Chuck, circa 1940, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05870)
    - Alexander, Chuck, circa 1940 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03891)
    - Alexander, Stewart (Skip), 1963 Oct. (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03892)
    - Beeson, Willard, 1957 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03893)
    - Benson, Jack, 1959 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03894)
    - Berner, Guy, 1939, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05871)
    - Berner, Guy, 1939 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03895)
    - Birmingham, John, circa 1959-1961 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03896)
    - Bolster, Denny, 1954 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03897)
    - Breed, Al, 1960 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03898)
    - Brownell, Bob, 1939, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05872)
    - Burden, Mark, 1976-1977 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03899)
    - Caldwell, Edwin "June," 1933, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05873)
    - Chapman, Frank, 1942, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05874)
    - Clark, Henry, 1953 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03900)
    - Cree, John, 1939, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05875)
    - Danluck, Tom, 1965 (after setting course record of 67 [or 68]) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03901)
    - Danluck, Tom, 1966 (co-captain) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03902)
    - Danluck, Tom (with Dan Hill, III), 1966 (co-captains) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03903)
    - Davis, Bruce, 1946 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03904)
    - Dawes, Ken, 1950 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03905)
    - DeBaufre, Tim, 1959 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03906)
    - Deupree, Bill, 1936, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05876)
    - DeWitt, Jack, 1941, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05877)
    - Dillon, George S., Jr. (Sandy), circa 1969 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03907)
    - Dillon, Grover, 1944, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05878)
    - Dion, Dick, 1960 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03908)
    - Disque, Jan, 1976 Apr. (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03909)
    - Doig, Bill, 1946, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05879)
    - Doig, Bill, 1946 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03910)
    - Doser, Jack, 1960 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03911)
    - Eisinger, John, 1954 (captain) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03912)
    - Fields, Bob, 1973 Apr. (golf award) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03913)
    - Foster, Dick, 1951 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03914)
    - Garrett, Frank, 1946 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03915)
    - Garrett, Tom, 1965 (after tying course record of 67 [or 68]) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03916)
    - Glagola, Charles, 1936, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05880)
    - Glenn, Bailey, 1947 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03917)
    - Goad, Art, 1939, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05881)
    - Goldthorp, 1942, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05882)
    - Gruber, Ira, 1953 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03918)
    - Hackett, Bob, 1954 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03919)
    - Hagler, Ellis "Dumpy" (Coach), 1959 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03920)
    - Hagler, Ellis "Dumpy" (Coach), undated (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03921)
    - Hahn, Paul (golf exhibitionist), 1959 May (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03922)
    - Hansen, Harald (not Harold), 1954 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03923)
    - Hardin, Paul, 1951 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03924)
    - Hicks, Betty, 1946 (visiting pro, men and women observing her) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03925)
    - Hill, Dan, III (putting) and Cliff Perry, 1965 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03926)
    - Hill, Dan, III, 1966 (co-captain) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03927)
    - Hindsley, Paul, 1980 Dec. (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03928)
    - Hood, Dick, 1954 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03929)
    - Hooker, Frank, 1953 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03930)
    - Ingold, John Rodman (Roddy), circa 1969 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03931)
    - Jennings, Bill, circa 1928-1930, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05883)
    - Jurgensen, Christian "Sonny," 1956 July (working on golf course) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03932)
    - Korcher, John, 1988-1989 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03933)
    - Lindinger, Bob, circa 1961 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03934)
    - Long, Claude, 1947 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03935)
    - McCanless, Fred, 1932, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05884)
    - McKenzie, Ted, circa 1960 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03936)
    - Miller, Garfield, 1939, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05885)
    - Myers, Rod (Coach), 1973 Aug. (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03937)
    - Nunn, Dewitt, 1942, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05886)
    - O'Donnell, Trip, 1966 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03938)
    - Perry, Cliff, 1936, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05887)
    - Perry, Tom, 1939 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03939)
    - Poe, Henry, 1936, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05888)
    - Pollock, Jim, 1950 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03940)
    - Poore, Pete, 1954 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03941)
    - Rankin, Bill, 1946 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03942)
    - Reed, Tony, 1950 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03943)
    - Schmid, Ron (Coach), 1974 Feb. (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03944)
    - Siderowf, Dick, 1959 (captain) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03945)
    - Smith, Luke, 1946 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03946)
    - Snead, Sam (exhibition), 1941 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03947)
    - Souchak, Mike, 1950, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05889)
    - Souchak, Mike, 1950 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03948)
    - Sronce, John, 1960 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03949)
    - Stokes, Earl, 1932, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05890)
    - Strickland, R. Michael, 1968 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03950)
    - Taylor, Joe, 1939, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05891)
    - Taylor, Joe, 1939 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03951)
    - Thomas, Ronnie (assistant golf pro), undated (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03952)
    - Toms, George, 1951 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03953)
    - Unidentified Golfer, 1971 Feb. (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03954)
    - Wall, Art, 1947, 1949 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03955)
    - Wall, Art (with Coach Ellis "Dumpy" Hagler), 1968 Apr. (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03956)
    - Widman, Mary Anne (image Hall of Fame portrait is based on), circa 1983-1984 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03957)
    - Wylie, John C., circa 1967 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03958)
    - Wylie, John C. (with Henry "Hy" Young), 1968 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03959)
    - Young, Henry "Hy," circa 1967 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03960)
    - Zimmerman, Bob, circa 1959-1960 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03961)
  - Groups, 37
    - Golfers, unidentified "Golf Course Group," 1957 June (men and women) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03962)
    - Golfers, unidentified, 1958 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03963)
    - Golfers, unidentified, 1962 May (photos taken for "picture story") (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03964)
    - Golfers, unidentified, 1964 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03965)
    - Golfers, unidentified, 1968 (National Women's Intercollegiate Golf Championships) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03966)
    - Golfers, unidentified, 1975 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03967)
    - Golfers, unidentified, 1980 (men's clinic) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03968)
  - Teams, 38
    - Team, 1928, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05892)
    - Team, 1929, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05893)
    - Team, 1930, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05894)
    - Team, 1932, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05895)
    - Team, 1934, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05896)
    - Team, 1939, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05897)
    - Team, 1946 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03969)
    - Team, 1947 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03970)
    - Team, 1951 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03971)
    - Team, 1953 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03972)
    - Team, 1957 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03973)
    - Team, 1958 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03974)
    - Team, 1959 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03975)
    - Team, 1960 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03976)
    - Team, 1964 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03977)
    - Team, 1968 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03978)
    - Team, 1969 (golfers identified) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03979)
    - Team, 1969 (golfers identified) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03980)
    - Team, 1971 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03981)
    - Team, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03982)
    - Team, 1976 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03983)
    - Team, 1977 Nov. (women) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03984)
    - Team, 1981 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03985)
  - Miscellaneous, 39
    - First players and trustees on new course, 1957 Sept. (men and women, unidentified) (3 sleeves) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03986)
    - First golf class on new course, 1957 Sept. (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03987)
    - Golf course - work on greens, 1957 Sept. (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03988)
    - First pro-shops at golf course, 1957 Oct. (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03989)
    - Golf course, 1957 Oct. (includes unidentified men and women) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03990)
    - First golf tournament on new course, 1958 May (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03991)
    - Unidentified individuals sitting on golf course, 1958 May 31 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03992)
    - Club house, holes 7, 12, and 13, 1962 March (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03993)
    - Aerial view of golf course, 1964 Aug. (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03994)
    - Aerial view of golf course, undated (color) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03995)
    - NCAA Golf Committee, 1962 March (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03996)
    - NCAA Pre-Publicity, 1962 June (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03997)
    - Purdue Golf Team, 1962 May (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03998)
    - Houston Golf Team, 1962 June (played in NCAA at Duke) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-03999)
- Gymnastics Negatives, 1935-1981; 11
  - Individual Athletes/Coaches/Staff, 40
    - Heckert, Dick, 1951 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04000)
    - Hedstrom, Don (Coach), circa 1951 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04001)
    - Lewis, Monk, 1938 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04002)
    - Miller, K. A. (coach), 1978 Apr. 20, 1981 Dec. (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04003)
    - Morton, Hilton, 1935-1936, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05898)
    - Nunn, Richard, 1951 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04004)
    - Waner, Paul, 1950 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04005)
  - Groups, 41
    - Gymnasts, unidentified, 1938, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05899)
    - Gymnasts, unidentified, 1954-1955 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04006)
  - Teams, 42
    - Team, 1951 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04007)
    - Team, 1955 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04008)
- Lacrosse Negatives, 1938-1981; undated; 12
  - Individual Athletes/Coaches/Staff, 43
    - Anderson, E. Everett, 1954 (copy negative made in 1974 Dec.) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04009)
    - Baker, Don (with Coach Jack Persons), 1954 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04010)
    - Bollinger, Dick (All-American), 1953-1954 (copy negative made in 1974 Dec.) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04011)
    - Boyce, Rod, 1951 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04012)
    - Boyce, Rod (with Jim Whitescarver), 1951 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04013)
    - Brown, Ray, 1940 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04014)
    - Bufford, Don, 1951 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04015)
    - Cassidy, Dennis (with Jeff Board) (co-captains), 1970 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04016)
    - Clark, Charles Branch, Jr. (Chuck), circa 1968 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04017)
    - Clausen, Don, 1951 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04018)
    - Corrie, Bruce (coach), 1968, 1971, 1972 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04019)
    - Corrie, Bruce (coach), undated (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04020)
    - Corrigan, Jim, 1946, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05900)
    - Cottman, Brooke, 1951 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04021)
    - Cullen, Tony (player and coach), circa 1977-1978, 1981 Nov. (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04022)
    - Dieffenbach, Otto, 1951 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04023)
    - Eisenbrandt, Fred, 1951 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04024)
    - Espey, John, 1976 Feb. (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04025)
    - Gilbert, Olin, 1946 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04026)
    - Gilfillan, Charles, 1949 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04027)
    - Gorsuch, Tom, 1946 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04028)
    - Hoshall, Lee, circa 1950-1951 (copy negative made in 1974 Dec.) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04029)
    - Koffenberger, Ed, 1947 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04030)
    - Neffgen, James (Jim), 1968 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04031)
    - Nuttle, Elbert R., Jr. (All-American), 1949 (copy negative made in 1974 Dec.) (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04032)
    - Peacock, Don, 1951 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04033)
    - Rogers, Nolan, 1953 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04034)
    - Ross, Walt, 1946 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04035)
    - Rutter, Don, 1951 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04036)
    - Sachs, Steve, crica 1968-1969 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04037)
    - Sachs, Steve (with Chuck Clark), 1969 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04038)
    - Saunders, Dick, 1956 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04039)
    - Scott, Don, 1956 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04040)
    - Shihadeh, Pete (with Tom Brodsky), 1970 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04041)
    - Snead, Phil (with Mal Travelstead) (co-captains), 1968 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04042)
    - Taylor, Bob, 1951 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04043)
    - Tremaine, Art, 1969 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04044)
    - Unidentified Player, 1967 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04045)
    - Unidentified Player, 1978 Apr. (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04046)
    - Unidentified Player and Coach, undated (Box 32)
  - Groups, 44
    - All-Stars (Thomas Gorsuch, Olin Gilbert, Walter Ross), 1946 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04047)
    - Bob Hanson, Charles Gilfillan, Fred Eisenbrandt, 1951 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04048)
    - Players, unidentified, 1954 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04049)
    - Players, unidentified, 1954 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04050)
    - Players, unidentified, 1955 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04051)
    - Players, unidentified, 1955 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04052)
    - Players, unidentified, 1955 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04053)
    - Players, unidentified, 1957 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04054)
    - Players, unidentified, 1963 Apr. (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04055)
    - Players, unidentified, 1967 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04056)
    - Mal Travelstead, Jim Neffgen, Steve Sachs, 1968 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04057)
    - Phil Snead, Lance Elliott, Nate Lane, Jack Neithammer, Don Goodkin, Bob Clift, Mal Travelstead, Coaches Roy Skinner and Bruce Corrie, 1968 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04058)
    - Midfield (Chuck Clark, Billy Snyder, Jim Watson, Jeff Board, Bill Pugh, Wood Struthers), 1969 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04059)
    - Steve Sachs, Chip Pettebone, Sam Grant, Newt Hasson, Morty Orman, Gary Townsend, Lee Miller, Coach Roy Skinner, 1969 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04060)
    - Jim Neffgen, Steve Sachs, Fred Ramsey, 1969 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04061)
    - Chip Pettebone, Sam Grant, Lee Miller, Gary Townsend, Newt Hasson, Coach Roy Skinner, 1970 (Box 32, Item UA13020018-N-04062)
    - Dennis Cassidy, Chip Pettebone, Art Tremaine, Al Cotrone, 1970 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04063)
    - Wes Chesson, Greg Vaniglia, Bob Parrish, Newt Hasson, 1970 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04064)
    - Jacque Passino, Ric Vosburgh, Jim Neffgen, Jon Brodsky, 1970 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04065)
    - Jim Neffgen, Ric Vosburgh, Bob Pinnella, Al Cotrone, Tom Brodsky, Jon Brodsky, Coach Bruce Corrie, 1970 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04066)
    - Lee Miller, Skip Walters, Jeff Board, Bill Pugh, Gary Townsend, Wood Struthers, Bill Snyder, Newt Hasson, 1970 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04067)
    - Players (co-captains), unidentified, 1971 Sept. (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04068)
    - Players (co-captains), unidentified, 1974 Sept. (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04069)
    - Players, unidentified, 1977 Apr. (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04070)
    - Players (co-captains), unidentified, 1978 Nov. (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04071)
    - Players, unidentified, 1979 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04072)
    - Players and Coach, unidentified, 1981 Feb. (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04073)
    - Players, unidentified, undated (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04074)
  - Teams, 45
    - Lacrosse Team (Duke's first), 1938, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05901)
    - Lacrosse Team, 1939, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05902)
    - Lacrosse Team, 1940, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05903)
    - Lacrosse Team, 1942, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05904)
    - Lacrosse Team, 1947 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04075)
    - Lacrosse Team, 1951 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04076)
    - Lacrosse Team, 1954 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04077)
    - Lacrosse Team, 1956 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04078)
    - Lacrosse Team, 1957 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04079)
    - Lacrosse Team, 1960 Mar. (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04080)
    - Lacrosse Team, 1967 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04081)
    - Lacrosse Team, 1968 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04082)
    - Lacrosse Team, 1969 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04083)
    - Lacrosse Team, 1970 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04084)
    - Lacrosse Team, 1971 Mar. (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04085)
    - Lacrosse Team, undated (copy negatives), 1972 Aug. (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04086)
    - Lacrosse Team, 1974 Mar. (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04087)
    - Lacrosse Team, 1975 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04088)
    - Lacrosse Team, 1977 Apr. (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04089)
    - Lacrosse Team, 1979 Apr. (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04090)
    - Lacrosse Team, 1980 Apr. (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04091)
    - Lacrosse Team, 1981 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04092)
  - Games, 46
    - Duke vs. Syracuse (first game at Duke), 1938, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05905)
    - Duke vs. Navy, 1956 May 5 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04093)
    - Duke vs. unidentified, 1960 March (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04094)
- Soccer Negatives, 1935-1990; undated; 13
  - Individual Athletes/Coaches/Staff, 47
    - Adler, Paul, 1974 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04095)
    - Cassaboon, John (Assistant Coach), 1980 Dec. (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04096)
    - Colmey, Tom, 1956 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04097)
    - Furniss, James (Mark), circa 1967, 1969 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04098)
    - Gauld, Ed, 1957 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04099)
    - Gerard, Gerry (Coach), 1937, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05906)
    - James, Fred, 1954 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04100)
    - Johnston, Pat, undated (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04101)
    - Jubanowsky, David Lyon (Dave), circa 1966 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04102)
    - Jubanowsky, David Lyon (Dave) (with Gordon Snyder), 1967 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04103)
    - Kain, Tom, circa 1984 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04104)
    - Kerr, John, circa 1986 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04105)
    - Leon-Ponte, Onardo, 1954 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04106)
    - Little, John, 1937, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-05907)
    - Morris, Doug, circa 1968 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04107)
    - Newbill, Jim, 1954 (Box 33, Item UA13020018-N-04108)